apcc.com 2004-06-11

# APC - Online Privacy Policy

The APC Online Privacy Policy provides information regarding accuracy, access, security and how APC controls client information acquired from its Website(s).

The _APC Website_ mission

The mission of the _APC Website_ is to provide clients with the most up-to-date product and company information and present it in a manner best suited to their needs. The _APC Website_ may be accessed by all Internet users on a 24/7 basis.

The _APC Website_ is the most accurate source of information on APC and its products/services. Questions regarding the accuracy of information on the _APC Website_ may be directed to the webmaster.

Handling of personal information

APC requests information from clients if they choose to subscribe to email lists, place orders or if they choose to respond to advertising, promotions, sweepstakes or contests. This personal information is necessary in order for APC to fulfill the client's request.

This information may also be used by APC to contact or update the client with periodic APC publications, product details or other special offers. APC does allow other reputable companies to offer special services or products of value to the client. The client may unsubscribe or request that their information not be shared by directing their request to [apccurrents@apcc.com](mailto:apccurrents@apcc.com). Please provide the exact name and address. In the case of email, only clients who have consented to receive email updates are included on email lists and instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from further solicitations is included in every such email they receive from APC. APC does not share email addresses with other companies. APC does not partner with or have any special relationships with any ad server companies.

From time to time, APC may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If information practices change at some time in the future APC will post the policy changes to the APC Website to notify the client of these changes and provide instructions to opt-out of these new uses. Clients concerned with how information is used, should check back at the APC Website periodically.

APC Website management uses IP addresses to diagnose Webserver problems and to administrate the APC Website. Cookies may be used to store client variables such as keeping track of the inventory of an online shopping cart, limiting repeated exposure to the same ads or bypassing login prompts by "remembering" passwords across sessions.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, APC may be contacted at [webmaster@apcc.com](mailto:webmaster@apcc.com).

APC E-Commerce Website(s)

The collection of personal information and similar transactions performed by the APC E-Commerce Website(s) are secured via SSL encryption. This information is used to process orders. Concerns regarding E-Commerce may be directed to [commercemaster@apcc.com](mailto:commercemaster@apcc.com).

APC is not interested in minors

APC has no desire to collect information from those under the age of 18. In an instance where such information were collected it would be purely accidental and unintentional. APC encourages parents to discuss the Internet with their children and monitor personal information that a child may provide via the Internet.
